JOHN LUCAS SCICLUNA

sciclunajl@gmail.com | 248-331-6379 | Okemos, MI 48864 | https://github.com/scicluna

Summary-

Enthusiastic and passionate individual seeking a junior software engineer position to work closely with professionals to develop and create applications and programs; test and update products.

Over five years' experience as an Accounts Payable Associate in finance and accounting.

-Tech Proficiencies-

JavascriptBootstrap

React

• PWA

ExpressJSMongoDB

HTML

NodeJS

CSS

Microsoft Word

SQL

Microsoft Excel

-Education-

- Edex MSU Fullstack Coding Bootcamp, 2022-2023
- Michigan State University, Eli Broad School of Business, East Lansing, MI, Bachelor of Arts: Accounting 05/2015. Overall GPA 3.7/4.0

-Experience-

Accounts Payable Associate | Delta Dental of Michigan - Okemos, MI | 03/2020 - 11/2022

- Paid vendors and verified accounts and payment totals.
- Carefully went over each invoice and requisition for payment.
- Reviewed invoices and expense reports to monitor expenditures.
- Worked with procurement to build payment vouchers and establish chains of approval.
- Managed vendor details, facilitating onboarding and collection of required documentation.
- Resolved various invoice issues driving on time entry and payment.
- Communicated and partnered with internal business partners to reduce roadblocks.
- Worked with vendors regarding AP functions by responding to email and telephone inquiries.
- Reconciled accounts by identifying errors or omissions, applying accounting standards.
- Approved payments and funding across departments to ensure that they me up audit-standards.

Casino Accounting Clerk | MGM Grand Detroit Casino - Detroit, MI | 07/2016 - 07/2019

- Organized and checked audit materials for lawful compliance.
- Analyzed end of month totals and reconciled inconsistencies throughout other departments.
- Cross trained in multiple internal auditing task.
- Supported clerical and administrative needs of senior department staff.